<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SBServices</string>
    <string name="text_register">Already Have An Account? Login Here</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>

    <string name="reqwdrshistry"> <u>Yours Rewards History</u></string>
    <string name="sbservices_text"> One call for all your project,Appartments  &amp; Home Cleaning Service needs</string>
    <string name="quick_affrod_trust"> Quick &#8226; Affordable &#8226; Trusted &#8226; Easy</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">Add to cart</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="update_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="label_network_error_message">Network Error</string>
    <string name="label_network_button_text">No internet connection !\\nPlease check your Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_mail">enter valid email</string>
    <string name="enter_name">enter name</string>
    <string name="enter_password">enter password</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_number">enter valid number</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_mobile_number">invalid mobile number</string>
    <string name="price_symbl">Rs</string>
    <string name="enter_door_number">enter door number</string>
    <string name="enter_landmark">fill this field</string>
    <string name="wallet">\u20B90</string>
    <string name="label_no_packages_available">Please contact this numbers:+91 9666688812 \n +91 9666409246</string>
    <string name="select_package">select package</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact us </string>
    <string name="notifictaion">Notifications</string>
    <string name="time_date">Time and Date</string>
    <string name="Edit_profile">EditProfile</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="cart_page">Cart</string>
    <string name="earn">Credit Points</string>
    <string name="payment_options">Select Payment Method</string>
    <!-- // <string name="select_package">select package</string>//-->
    <string name="my_account">MyAccount</string>
    <string name="my_orders">MyOrders</string>
    <string name="edittext_phone"><font size="10">Phone Number</font></string>
    <string name="address">Sb Services\nVijayawada\n</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="imgdesc">imgdesc</string>

    <string name="time_slot_one">7Am-9Am</string>
    <string name="privacy">PERSONAL INFORMATION

User referred to as (“You”) and SB on Call Services hereinafter referred to as (“SB SERVICES”). SB SERVICES is owner and operator of www.sbservices.in (“the Website”), SB SERVICES Mobile Application for your requirements fulfill home &amp; offices services (“sb services App”) and the Website “sbservices.in”

At the time of using the SB Services you will share certain Personal Information with sb services, SB SERVICES respects your Personal Information. Such Personal Information may include your personal identifiable information such as your name, address, mobile number, your e-mail ids, your age, IP address, payment details and any other personal information which You may share in connection with the services.

When you use SB services’ Service through SB SERVICES App, SB SERVICES may use Your mobile device’s ID (the unique identification assigned to a mobile device by the manufacturer). SB SERVICES does this to store your preferences and track your use of SB SERVICES App. You understand and agree that SB SERVICES has every right to share such ID with third parties for its promotions, analysis, etc.

In case You participate in any other schemes, facilities, services provided by the SB SERVICES Service, You will be required to provide additional information. Such information will also remain in SBSERVICES’s database and will be considered as your Personal Information and will be treated as confidential.

Pre-approved Sharing of Personal Information

SB SERVICES endeavors to protect your Personal Information. SB SERVICES may share your Personal Information with its sponsors, service providers and its business partners. Personal information collected from You and other users may be analyzed in different manners. SB SERVICES may also share such analysis with its service providers and its business partners.

In case SB SERVICES is required to disclose your Personal Information in order to assist the Government Authority or in adherence to the Court or to protect the interest of the SB SERVICES Service and/or any particular user(s), SB SERVICES will disclose it without obtaining prior permission from you.

This Privacy Policy applies only to the SB Services. The Services may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by SB SERVICES (the "Third Party Sites"). The policies we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

Changes to Privacy Policy

SB SERVICES have and continue to have the right to modify, change or update Privacy Policy at any time. However, sb services will use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with Privacy Policy at the time you shared Personal Information. You are encouraged to check the sb services often to get updated about Privacy Policy. You acknowledge that by virtue of usage of the SB Service you provide acceptance of the Privacy Policy. All questions to be addressed to Email:- sbservice222@gmail.com.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

# 302, DRWA,

Devi nagar, 2nd road,

vijayawada - 520003

andhra pradesh- INDIA

mob:- 9666688812

sbservice222@gmail.com

Terms of Use
Welcome to sb services. You may use our services through our website www.sbservices.in (“Website”) or our mobile application (“ sb service App”). Whether accessible to you via web, mobile App or other platform (our services, together with the Site, are the "Services")

Dear customer When You use any of the Services provided by Us, including but not limited to, Electrical, Plumbing, Computer Repair, Carpentry etc, you will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service, and they shall be deemed to be incorporated into this Terms of Use and shall be considered as part and parcel of these Terms of Use. As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, We grant you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use our platforms. In the event of a conflict or inconsistency between any provision of the terms and conditions mentioned herein with those of the particular service, the provisions of the terms and conditions applicable to such specific Services shall prevail.

HOME CLEANING

Before initiating the job at your premises, please confirm with your SB TEAM the areas included &amp; excluded for the service that you have selected.

We strongly advise you to make sure that all your belongings are carefully kept in a secure location. Please make sure that any sensitive material is carefully moved under your supervision only. Also, when our team is leaving your premises, please make sure that you have thoroughly checked the entire home.

REFUNDS &amp; REWORKS

For any issues related to the quality of service, call our support team on 9666688812.

Any complaints in respect of the service should be raised within 24 hours from the service. In the event that any rework or refund is to be processed for the service it shall be initiated only within the warranty period for the respective service.

In the event that any rework is to be performed for any services that has already been rendered via a service provider (“SB TEAM”), SB SERVICE should be contacted directly 9666688812. Please do not call the SB TEAM directly. In the event that any Customer directly contacts the SB TEAM: SB SERVICE will not responsible for any actions or behavior of the SB TEAM, nor will it be responsible for any consequences thereof.

The Customer shall have waived his / her / its right to any service warranty that may have been provided at the time of booking.

The rework of any rendered service would be done by either a SB TEAM or a third party appointed by SB SERVICES (at the discretion of SB services).

Please report any payment or invoicing related issues within 48 (Forty Eight) hours of the job closure.

 </string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">1.In order to use the Service, you must first agree to the Terms. You may not use the Service if you do not accept the Terms.\n2.You can accept the Terms by clicking to accept or agree to the Terms, where this option is made available to you by Google.\n
3.You may not use the Service and may not accept the Terms if you are not of legal age to form a binding contract with Google.

</string>
    <string name="login_using">Login using Email or Social Accounts</string>
    <string name="rating">How likely are you to recommend SB Services App </string>
    <string name="cumstmr_paid">customerPaid</string>
    <string name="sub_totsal">sub Total</string>
    <string name="disscount">Disscount</string>
    <string name="grabnd_total">Grand Total</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">2340225882907109</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb2340225882907109</string>
    <string name="channel_name">SB</string>
    <string name="channcel_desc">SBSERVICES</string>
    <string name="msg_subscribed">Subscribed</string>
    <string name="msg_subscribe_failed">failed</string>
</resources>
